[
  {
    "Front": "ὦ",
    "Back": " interjektion: o (bruges ved henvendelse)"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὧδε",
    "Back": " adv.: således"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὠθέω",
    "Back": " vb.: støder til"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὠνέοµαι",
    "Back": " vb.: køber"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὥρα",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: time"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὡς",
    "Back": " konj.: som, ligesom; da; at"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὡς",
    "Back": " præp. m. akk.: hen til"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὡσαύτως",
    "Back": " adv.: ligesådan"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὥσπερ",
    "Back": " konj.: sådan som"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὥστε",
    "Back": " konj. $: så at"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὠφέλεια",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: nytte"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὠφελέω",
    "Back": " vb.: gavner"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὠφέλιµος",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: gavnlig"
  }
]